<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Alerting on INFINI Console</title><link>/console/main/docs/reference/alerting/</link><description>Recent content in Alerting on INFINI Console</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><atom:link href="/console/main/docs/reference/alerting/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Alerting Center</title><link>/console/main/docs/reference/alerting/message/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/console/main/docs/reference/alerting/message/</guid><description>Alerting center # Introduction # By default, the message center displays the alerting events that are currently occurring in the system, which is convenient for administrators to quickly preview the execution status of the system.
Message list # The message list aggregates all triggered alerting events. If each alerting rule repeatedly triggers multiple alerting messages, only one will be aggregated and displayed here. Click the details to see more information.</description></item><item><title>Alerting Rules</title><link>/console/main/docs/reference/alerting/rule/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/console/main/docs/reference/alerting/rule/</guid><description>Alerting Rules # Introduction # The alerting rules include the configuration of four parts: data source, metrics definition, trigger condition, and message notification
Alerting rules list # In the alerting rules list, you can query the alerting rules that have been added
New alerting rule # Click the New button in the alerting rule list to enter the new alerting rule page
Configure data source # Select a cluster (required) Select index, support input index pattern (required) Input elasticsearch query DSL query filter conditions (optional) Select time field (required) Select the statistical period (for time field aggregation, the default is one minute) Configure alerting metrics and trigger conditions # Input the rule name Add the grouped fields and group size as needed, you can add more than one for terms aggregation Select the metrics aggregation field and statistics type, you can configure more than one, when configuring more than one, you must configure a formula to calculate the final metrics Configure alerting trigger conditions Select execution check cycle Input the title of the alerting event (template, referenced by the title in the template variable, click here to learn about template syntax ) Input alerting event message (template, referenced by message in template variable, click here for template syntax ) Configure message notification # Configure notification channels, which can be reconfigured, or you can use the add button to select an already created channel as a template to quickly fill in, and support adding multiple Choose whether to enable notification upgrades as needed Select silence period (how often notification messages are sent) Configure notification sending time period Click the save button to submit Update alerting rules # Select the alerting rule to be updated in the alerting rules list and click the Edit button to enter the update alerting rules page</description></item><item><title>Alerting Channels</title><link>/console/main/docs/reference/alerting/channel/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/console/main/docs/reference/alerting/channel/</guid><description>Alerting Channels # Introduction # The alerting channel is used to configure the channel for sending notification messages when an alerting rule is triggered. Currently, webhook is supported.
Channes list # In the channels list, you can query the channels that have been added
New alerting channel # Click the New button on the channels list page to enter the new alerting channel page
Input channel name (required) Select channel type (currently only webhook is supported) Input the webhook address Select the method of HTTP request, the default is POST Add HTTP request headers as needed Configure the webhook request body Click the save button to submit Update channel configuration # Select the channel to be updated in the channels list and click the Edit button to enter the update channel configuration page</description></item><item><title>Template variables</title><link>/console/main/docs/reference/alerting/variables/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/console/main/docs/reference/alerting/variables/</guid><description>Template variables # Introduction # When custom alerting triggers event content, in addition to the fixed copy written by yourself, the event title and event content also support template syntax. The rendering of the text can be achieved using fields in the event.
Variables # The syntax for rendering fields is {{ .fieldname }}, and the variable fields that can be used for template content rendering are as follows:</description></item></channel></rss>