<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Core Features on Coco AI App</title><link>/coco-app/v0.10.0/docs/core-features/</link><description>Recent content in Core Features on Coco AI App</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><atom:link href="/coco-app/v0.10.0/docs/core-features/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>AI Overview</title><link>/coco-app/v0.10.0/docs/core-features/AI-Overview/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/coco-app/v0.10.0/docs/core-features/AI-Overview/</guid><description>AI Overview # The AI Overview feature can automatically refine and summarize current search results in search mode, helping users quickly grasp the key points of the search results without having to browse each individual result. This feature is particularly useful in scenarios where information needs to be extracted quickly.
Feature Overview # Automatic Refinement and Summary: When a user performs a search, AI Overview automatically generates a concise summary based on the current search results, providing key information from the results.</description></item><item><title>Quick AI Access</title><link>/coco-app/v0.10.0/docs/core-features/Quick-AI-Access/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/coco-app/v0.10.0/docs/core-features/Quick-AI-Access/</guid><description>Quick AI Access # The Quick AI Access feature allows you to directly start a conversation with AI through the search box without switching to chat mode. This feature provides users with a smoother and more efficient interaction experience, especially suitable for scenarios where quick feedback or handling simple questions is needed.
Feature Overview # Quickly Start a Conversation: After entering content in the search box, press Meta + Enter to directly start a conversation with the AI assistant without switching to chat mode.</description></item><item><title>File Search</title><link>/coco-app/v0.10.0/docs/core-features/File-Search/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/coco-app/v0.10.0/docs/core-features/File-Search/</guid><description>File Search # The File Search feature allows you to directly use the system&amp;rsquo;s local search capability in Coco AI to quickly find files on your computer. You can flexibly set the search scope, excluded directories, file types, and search methods to get more accurate results.
Feature Overview # System-level search integration: Coco AI leverages the file indexing capabilities provided by the operating system (such as macOS Spotlight, Windows Search, etc.</description></item><item><title>Application Search</title><link>/coco-app/v0.10.0/docs/core-features/Application-Search/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/coco-app/v0.10.0/docs/core-features/Application-Search/</guid><description>Application Search # The Applications feature allows you to directly search for and launch locally installed applications in Coco AI. You can quickly find and open any application through the unified search entry without switching windows or manually searching.
Feature Overview # Quick Launch: Enter the application name in the search box to instantly match results and quickly open the program.
Custom Search Scope: Control which directories' applications are indexed and displayed through settings.</description></item><item><title>Calculator</title><link>/coco-app/v0.10.0/docs/core-features/Calculator/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/coco-app/v0.10.0/docs/core-features/Calculator/</guid><description>Calculator # Coco AI provides a concise calculator function that allows users to perform quickquick basic mathematical calculations directly in the input box without opening a separate calculator application. Simply enter an arithmetic expression, and the system will instantly provide the result. It also supports copying the arithmetic expression and the calculation result for easy use at any time.
Feature Overview # Quick Calculation: Enter basic mathematical expressions in Coco AI&amp;rsquo;s input box, and the system will automatically calculate and display the result.</description></item><item><title>Window Management</title><link>/coco-app/v0.10.0/docs/core-features/Window-Management/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/coco-app/v0.10.0/docs/core-features/Window-Management/</guid><description>Window Management # Easily adjust, reorganize, and move the windows you&amp;rsquo;re focusing on. No need for manual dragging—quickly perform window layout operations through commands.
Feature Overview # Move Windows: Move the current window to the left half, right half, top half, or bottom half of the screen. Resize Windows: Quickly adjust to full screen, centered, 1/3, or 2/3 size layouts. Multi-monitor Support: Quickly move windows between multiple monitors.</description></item></channel></rss>