<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Data Management on INFINI Console</title><link>/console/v1.29.6/docs/reference/data/</link><description>Recent content in Data Management on INFINI Console</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><atom:link href="/console/v1.29.6/docs/reference/data/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Index</title><link>/console/v1.29.6/docs/reference/data/indices/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/console/v1.29.6/docs/reference/data/indices/</guid><description>Index management # Index list # The index list includes addition, deletion, modification, and lookup operations on indexes.
New index # Input the new index name and index settings to complete the addition.
Index details # You can view the index health status, number of shards, number of documents, storage size and other details, as well as view and modify Mappings and Edit settings.</description></item><item><title>Alias</title><link>/console/v1.29.6/docs/reference/data/alias/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/console/v1.29.6/docs/reference/data/alias/</guid><description>Alias Management # Alias list # The alias list includes addition, deletion, modification, and search operations for aliases.
New alias # Alias: Input an alias name Index: Select the target index corresponding to the alias, and use (*) to bind multiple indexes. Is Write Index: specify whether the selected index is writable. If the alias only binds one index, the index is writable by default; if multiple indexes are bound by (*), it is most necessary to specify one of the indexes as writable .</description></item><item><title>Data View</title><link>/console/v1.29.6/docs/reference/data/view/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/console/v1.29.6/docs/reference/data/view/</guid><description>Data View # View list # Creating and managing data views can help you better get data from Elasticsearch.
Create data view # Step 1 Define the data view # Input a view name Matching rules: Match the corresponding index, you can also use (*) to match multiple indexes. Step 2 Configuration # Select time field as time filter for view index</description></item></channel></rss>