<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Coco AI App</title><link>/coco-app/v0.10.0/</link><description>Recent content on Coco AI App</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><atom:link href="/coco-app/v0.10.0/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>AI Overview</title><link>/coco-app/v0.10.0/docs/core-features/AI-Overview/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/coco-app/v0.10.0/docs/core-features/AI-Overview/</guid><description>AI Overview # The AI Overview feature can automatically refine and summarize current search results in search mode, helping users quickly grasp the key points of the search results without having to browse each individual result. This feature is particularly useful in scenarios where information needs to be extracted quickly.
Feature Overview # Automatic Refinement and Summary: When a user performs a search, AI Overview automatically generates a concise summary based on the current search results, providing key information from the results.</description></item><item><title>Quick AI Access</title><link>/coco-app/v0.10.0/docs/core-features/Quick-AI-Access/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/coco-app/v0.10.0/docs/core-features/Quick-AI-Access/</guid><description>Quick AI Access # The Quick AI Access feature allows you to directly start a conversation with AI through the search box without switching to chat mode. This feature provides users with a smoother and more efficient interaction experience, especially suitable for scenarios where quick feedback or handling simple questions is needed.
Feature Overview # Quickly Start a Conversation: After entering content in the search box, press Meta + Enter to directly start a conversation with the AI assistant without switching to chat mode.</description></item><item><title>The Basics</title><link>/coco-app/v0.10.0/docs/getting-started/The-Basics/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/coco-app/v0.10.0/docs/getting-started/The-Basics/</guid><description>The Basics # Coco AI is always ready to help you quickly go from &amp;ldquo;wanting to ask&amp;rdquo; to &amp;ldquo;finding answers&amp;rdquo;. This page will briefly introduce the core concepts and quick start process of Coco AI.
Core Operations # Use the global shortcut (default: Shift + Meta + Space) to open the Coco AI interface. In the interface, use the toggle button or shortcut key (default: Meta + T) to switch between search and AI chat modes.</description></item><item><title>File Search</title><link>/coco-app/v0.10.0/docs/core-features/File-Search/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/coco-app/v0.10.0/docs/core-features/File-Search/</guid><description>File Search # The File Search feature allows you to directly use the system&amp;rsquo;s local search capability in Coco AI to quickly find files on your computer. You can flexibly set the search scope, excluded directories, file types, and search methods to get more accurate results.
Feature Overview # System-level search integration: Coco AI leverages the file indexing capabilities provided by the operating system (such as macOS Spotlight, Windows Search, etc.</description></item><item><title>Search</title><link>/coco-app/v0.10.0/docs/getting-started/Search/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/coco-app/v0.10.0/docs/getting-started/Search/</guid><description>Search # Coco AI&amp;rsquo;s search function is designed to provide a unified, intelligent, and efficient cross-platform information retrieval experience. In search mode, you can quickly find local files, applications, commands, extensions, data sources in Coco Server (including Google Drive, Notion, Yuque, Hugo sites, RSS, Github, Postgres, etc.), and AI assistants through the search box.
Search Entrance # Open the Coco AI interface using the global shortcut (default: Shift + Meta + Space).</description></item><item><title>AI Chat</title><link>/coco-app/v0.10.0/docs/getting-started/AI-Chat/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/coco-app/v0.10.0/docs/getting-started/AI-Chat/</guid><description>AI Chat # Coco AI is not just a search tool, but your AI intelligent center. In chat mode, you can communicate with AI in natural language, ask questions, analyze files, and summarize knowledge.
Chat Entry # Use the global shortcut (default: Shift + Meta + Space) to open the Coco AI interface.
The interface is in chat mode (use the switch button or the shortcut Meta + T to switch modes).</description></item><item><title>Application Search</title><link>/coco-app/v0.10.0/docs/core-features/Application-Search/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/coco-app/v0.10.0/docs/core-features/Application-Search/</guid><description>Application Search # The Applications feature allows you to directly search for and launch locally installed applications in Coco AI. You can quickly find and open any application through the unified search entry without switching windows or manually searching.
Feature Overview # Quick Launch: Enter the application name in the search box to instantly match results and quickly open the program.
Custom Search Scope: Control which directories' applications are indexed and displayed through settings.</description></item><item><title>Calculator</title><link>/coco-app/v0.10.0/docs/core-features/Calculator/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/coco-app/v0.10.0/docs/core-features/Calculator/</guid><description>Calculator # Coco AI provides a concise calculator function that allows users to perform quickquick basic mathematical calculations directly in the input box without opening a separate calculator application. Simply enter an arithmetic expression, and the system will instantly provide the result. It also supports copying the arithmetic expression and the calculation result for easy use at any time.
Feature Overview # Quick Calculation: Enter basic mathematical expressions in Coco AI&amp;rsquo;s input box, and the system will automatically calculate and display the result.</description></item><item><title>Extension</title><link>/coco-app/v0.10.0/docs/getting-started/Extension/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/coco-app/v0.10.0/docs/getting-started/Extension/</guid><description>Extension # Extensions of Coco AI are plug-in modules that add specific functions to the core system. By installing extensions, you can greatly enhance the capabilities of Coco AI and create a personalized intelligent working environment.
How to Install Extensions # Install via Extension Store # In the Extension Store, you can browse or search for the required extensions. After finding the desired extension, press ↵ to view details, and click the install button on the details page.</description></item><item><title>Keyboard Shortcuts</title><link>/coco-app/v0.10.0/docs/getting-started/Keyboard-Shortcuts/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/coco-app/v0.10.0/docs/getting-started/Keyboard-Shortcuts/</guid><description>Keyboard Shortcuts # Coco AI provides an intuitive set of keyboard shortcuts to help you navigate efficiently, execute commands, switch modes, and manage conversations. Mastering these shortcuts can greatly enhance your user experience.
You don&amp;rsquo;t need to memorize the shortcuts # Simply go to Settings (shortcut: Meta + ,) → General → Tooltip, and turn on the shortcut hint switch. After enabling, when you hold down the modifier key, the corresponding shortcut hints will be displayed in real-time in each functional area of the interface.</description></item><item><title>Window Management</title><link>/coco-app/v0.10.0/docs/core-features/Window-Management/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/coco-app/v0.10.0/docs/core-features/Window-Management/</guid><description>Window Management # Easily adjust, reorganize, and move the windows you&amp;rsquo;re focusing on. No need for manual dragging—quickly perform window layout operations through commands.
Feature Overview # Move Windows: Move the current window to the left half, right half, top half, or bottom half of the screen. Resize Windows: Quickly adjust to full screen, centered, 1/3, or 2/3 size layouts. Multi-monitor Support: Quickly move windows between multiple monitors.</description></item><item><title>Settings</title><link>/coco-app/v0.10.0/docs/getting-started/Settings/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/coco-app/v0.10.0/docs/getting-started/Settings/</guid><description>Settings # In Coco AI, you can adjust various settings of the application according to your personal needs (shortcut: Meta + ,) . The settings page is divided into several main sections, allowing you to easily manage startup items, shortcuts, extensions, connections, and advanced features.
General # In the General Settings section, you can adjust Coco AI&amp;rsquo;s startup items, startup shortcuts, interface appearance, and language.
Extension # In the Extension Settings, you can view, manage, and configure installed extensions.</description></item><item><title>macOS</title><link>/coco-app/v0.10.0/docs/getting-started/installation/macos/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/coco-app/v0.10.0/docs/getting-started/installation/macos/</guid><description>macOS # Download Coco AI # Go to coco.rs and download the package of your architecture:
It should be placed in your &amp;ldquo;Downloads&amp;rdquo; folder:
Unzip DMG file # Unzip the file:
You will get a dmg file:
Drag to Application Folder # Double click the dmg file, a window will pop up. Then drag the &amp;ldquo;Coco-AI&amp;rdquo; app to your &amp;ldquo;Applications&amp;rdquo; folder:</description></item><item><title>Screenshot</title><link>/coco-app/v0.10.0/docs/getting-started/screenshot/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/coco-app/v0.10.0/docs/getting-started/screenshot/</guid><description>Screenshot # Screenshot Gallery # Here are some screenshots showcasing the user interface:
Search Local Desktop Applications Seamlessly search through your local apps directly from Coco AI.
Search Across Personal &amp;amp; Enterprise Knowledge Bases
Perform hybrid searches across multiple data sources, including personal and company knowledge bases.
Chat with Your AI Assistant
Interact with the AI assistant, which leverages your personal knowledge base to provide detailed and intelligent answers.</description></item><item><title>Ubuntu</title><link>/coco-app/v0.10.0/docs/getting-started/installation/ubuntu/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/coco-app/v0.10.0/docs/getting-started/installation/ubuntu/</guid><description>Ubuntu # NOTE: Coco app only works fully under X11.
Don&amp;rsquo;t know if you running X11 or not? take a look at this question!
Install dependencies # $ sudo apt-get update $ sudo apt-get install -y libwebkit2gtk-4.1-dev libappindicator3-dev librsvg2-dev patchelf xdg-utils libtracker-sparql-3.0-dev Go to the download page # Download page: link
Download the package # Download the package of your architecture, it should be put in your Downloads directory and look like this:</description></item><item><title>Windows</title><link>/coco-app/v0.10.0/docs/getting-started/installation/windows/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/coco-app/v0.10.0/docs/getting-started/installation/windows/</guid><description>Windows # Download Coco AI # Goto https://coco.rs/
Install Wizard #</description></item></channel></rss>