<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Tutorials on INFINI Console</title><link>/console/v1.28.0/docs/tutorials/</link><description>Recent content in Tutorials on INFINI Console</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><atom:link href="/console/v1.28.0/docs/tutorials/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>How to easily create an Elasticsearch "guest" user</title><link>/console/v1.28.0/docs/tutorials/create_readonly_account/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/console/v1.28.0/docs/tutorials/create_readonly_account/</guid><description>How to easily create an Elasticsearch &amp;ldquo;guest&amp;rdquo; user # Introduction # In some cases, we want to share some functions or data with customers, but do not want the data to be modified. At this point we need to create a &amp;ldquo;guest&amp;rdquo; user. This article briefly describes how to create a &amp;ldquo;guest&amp;rdquo; user using the INFINI Console.
Prepare # Download and install the latest version of INFINI Console Enable INFINI Console Security Features Creating a Role # Click System &amp;gt; Security Settings on the left menu of INFINI Console, and select the Role Tab page to enter the role management page.</description></item><item><title>How to assign different Elasticsearch cluster access permissions to different INFINI Console accounts</title><link>/console/v1.28.0/docs/tutorials/role_with_different_rights/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/console/v1.28.0/docs/tutorials/role_with_different_rights/</guid><description>How to assign different Elasticsearch cluster access permissions to different INFINI Console accounts # Introduction # This article will introduce the use of INFINI Console to assign two different Elasticsearch cluster management permissions to two different accounts
Prepare # Download and install the latest version of INFINI Console Enable INFINI Console Security Features Register at least two Elasticsearch clusters to the INFINI Console Creating a Role # Click System &amp;gt; Security Settings on the left menu of INFINI Console, and select the Role Tab page to enter the role management page.</description></item><item><title>How to assign Elasticsearch index-level permissions to INFINI Console accounts</title><link>/console/v1.28.0/docs/tutorials/role_with_index_limit/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/console/v1.28.0/docs/tutorials/role_with_index_limit/</guid><description>How to assign Elasticsearch index-level permissions to INFINI Console accounts # Introduction # This article will introduce the use of INFINI Console to limit an account to only have the management permissions of certain indexes in the Elasticsearch cluster
Prepare # Download and install the latest version of INFINI Console Enable INFINI Console Security Features Register at least two Elasticsearch clusters to the INFINI Console Creating a Role # Click System &amp;gt; Security Settings on the left menu of INFINI Console, and select the Role Tab page to enter the role management page.</description></item><item><title>How to Monitor Elasticsearch Cluster Health</title><link>/console/v1.28.0/docs/tutorials/cluster_health_change/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/console/v1.28.0/docs/tutorials/cluster_health_change/</guid><description>How to Monitor Elasticsearch Cluster Health # Introduction # In many cases, the cluster health status of the Elasticsearch cluster will turn red for some reason. At this time, at least one primary shard in the Elasticsearch cluster is unallocated or lost. So it is necessary to monitor the health status of the Elasticsearch cluster. This article will introduce how to use the INFINI Console alerting feature to monitor the health of an Elasticsearch cluster.</description></item><item><title>How to monitor Elasticsearch cluster node disk usage</title><link>/console/v1.28.0/docs/tutorials/cluster_node_disk_usage/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/console/v1.28.0/docs/tutorials/cluster_node_disk_usage/</guid><description>How to monitor Elasticsearch cluster node disk usage # Introduction # When the system disk usage is too high, data cannot be written into the Elasticsearch cluster, which is likely to result in data loss. Therefore, monitor the Elasticsearch cluster. Node disk usage is necessary. This article will show you how to monitor your Elasticsearch cluster using INFINI Console alerts Node disk usage.
Prepare # Download and install the latest version of INFINI Console Register Elasticsearch cluster using INFINI Console Create alerting rule # Open INFINI Console in the browser, click on the left menu &amp;ldquo;Alerting&amp;rdquo; &amp;gt; Rules to enter the alerting management page, and then click New button to enter the Create Alerting Rule page.</description></item><item><title>How to monitor slow query requests in Elasticsearch</title><link>/console/v1.28.0/docs/tutorials/cluster_slow_request/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/console/v1.28.0/docs/tutorials/cluster_slow_request/</guid><description>How to monitor slow query requests in Elasticsearch # Introduction # Many times, the Elasticsearch cluster will experience peak data writing or query traffic. At this time, the Elasticsearch cluster will be under a lot of pressure. Through the monitoring and alertinging of the delay of the Elasticsearch index query. This allows us to locate which indexes are the most stressed on the Elasticsearch cluster. This article will introduce how to use the INFINI Console alerting function to monitor the slow query request index in Elasticsearch.</description></item><item><title>How to monitor the CPU usage of Elasticsearch cluster nodes</title><link>/console/v1.28.0/docs/tutorials/cluster_node_cpu_usage/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/console/v1.28.0/docs/tutorials/cluster_node_cpu_usage/</guid><description>How to monitor the CPU usage of Elasticsearch cluster nodes # Introduction # This article will introduce how to use the INFINI Console to monitor the disk usage of Elasticsearch cluster nodes and alert them.
Prepare # Download and install the latest version of INFINI Console Register Elasticsearch cluster using INFINI Console Create alerting rule # Open INFINI Console in the browser, click Alerting &amp;gt; Rules on the left menu to enter the alerting management page, and then click the New button to enter the alerting rule creation page.</description></item><item><title>How to monitor JVM usage of Elasticsearch cluster nodes</title><link>/console/v1.28.0/docs/tutorials/cluster_node_jvm_usage/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/console/v1.28.0/docs/tutorials/cluster_node_jvm_usage/</guid><description>How to monitor JVM usage of Elasticsearch cluster nodes # Introduction # This article will introduce how to use the INFINI Console to monitor the JVM usage of Elasticsearch cluster nodes and generate alerts.
Prepare # Download and install the latest version of INFINI Console Register Elasticsearch cluster using INFINI Console Create alerting rule # Open INFINI Console in the browser, click on the left menu &amp;ldquo;Alerting&amp;rdquo; &amp;gt; Rules to enter the alerting management page, and then click New button to enter the Create Alerting Rule page.</description></item></channel></rss>